

Agustin Llado

Professional Summary

I am a results-oriented Test Automation Engineer with most experience in C# and JAVA. Flexible and resourceful professional with deep understanding of acceptance criteria and testing scenarios. Always ready to employ automation methodologies to maximize quality assurance efficiency and testing quality.

Work History

Endava – Automation Engineer

04/2021 - Current

- Create automation test scripts in C# for multiple client applications
- API testing
- Framework maintenance and refactor
- Discussed requirements and processes with project managers and team
- Update and maintain project documentation

NetSuite - Solution Consultant

03/2019 - 04/2021

- Create automation tools to supplant manual tasks using technologies as Java, TestNG and Selenium WebDriver.
- Manage projects versioning using Oracle's SCM and GitFlow methodology.
- Established project automation methodology, frameworks and tools
- Reviewed all test cases and test scripts for quality and purposely looked for additional areas to review
- Completed automation of functional and regression testing
- Updated and maintained project documentation
- Looked for ways to improve review processes and reviewed all test cases and scripts for quality

Altimetrik Uruguay - Quality Assurance Analyst

11/2015 - 03/2019

- Created accurate and efficient test scripts to manage automated testing of certain products and features
- Reviewed project requirements to uncover bugs and resolve issues within a timely manner

lladoagustin@gmail.com 598-098-358991 21 de Setiembre 3108/103 , Montevideo, Montevideo 11300

Skills and Technologies

- Automation design
- TestNG, Junit, NUnit
- Selenium WebDriver
- C#, Java, JavaScript
- SQL
- Git
- Testing scripts
- Agile methodologies
- Software testing
- Unit Testing / TDD
- API Testing

Education

02/2013

Saint George's School

Montevideo, Departamento de

Montevideo

High School Diploma

Universidad ORT Uruguay (Campus Center)

Montevideo, Departamento de Montevideo

Actually studying "Licenciatura en Sistemas".

- Collaborated with developers and product owners to stay current on product features and intended functionality
- Created and achieved product quality objectives and met product specifications

TATA Consultancy Services - Quality Assurance Analyst 06/2015 - 11/2015

• Wrote and optimized test cases to maximize success of manual software testing with consistent, thorough approaches